Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Research Program Files
  - Subseries A. Grants Awarded
    - Subsubseries 2. Grant Program files
      - B. Grant Products files
        - G524, Nisbett, John, et al. John Holland, Induction: Processes of Inference, Learning and Discovery,1986 (Box 101, Folder 6)
          [NOTE: See related material for Grant #314 in Box II-69, folders 5-10]
        - G550[and G236], Hudspeth, A. James. Papers received June 2, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 1)
        - G550, Hudspeth, A. James. Papers received 1984-1986 (Box 102, Folder 2)
        - G554, Marlow, W. H. Papers, 1983-1986 (Box 102, Folder 3)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Math Companion for Computer Science, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 4)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Introduction to the Theory of Automata, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 5)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Papers received Dec. 9, 1985-Aug. 18, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 6)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports received Dec. 10, 1986 #1 (Box 102, Folder 7)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports received #2 Dec. 10, 1986 #1 (Box 103, Folder 1)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports received #3 Dec. 10, 1986 #1 (Box 103, Folder 2)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports received #1Apr. 13, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 3)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports received #2Apr. 13, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 4)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Papers received #1Sept. 12, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 5)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Papers received #2Sept. 12, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 6)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Papers received #3Sept. 12, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 1)
        - G565, Bavel, Zamir. Reports receivedSept. 30, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 2)
        - G566, Mari, Jean Francois. Papers, 1985 and 1986 (Box 104, Folder 3)
        - G575, Gaves, Henson. Algos: A Foundation for the Representation of Knowledge, draft received Aug. 13, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 4)
        - G575, Gaves, Henson. Algos: A Foundation for the Representation of Knowledge, bound copy received Aug. 14, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 5)
        - G575, Gaves, Henson. Papers received June 21, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 6)
        - G576, Bell, Gwen. Mailings received Mar. 1984-June 1987 (Box 104, Folder 7)
        - G590, Weinstein, Scott. Papers received May 5, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 8)
        - G592, Greenough, William. Papers, 1985-1987 (Box 104, Folder 9)
        - G600[a-b], Traub, J. F. Papers received Aug. 1984-Apr. 1987 (Box 104, Folder 10)
        - G600[a-b], Traub, J. F. Journal of Complexity, v. 1, no. 1, Oct. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 1)
        - G612, Lander, Eric. Papers received Sept. 17, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 2)
        - G612, Lander, Eric. Papers received #1Oct. 5, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 3)
        - G612, Lander, Eric. Papers received #2Oct. 5, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 4)
        - G612, Lander, Eric. Papers,1987-1988 (Box 105, Folder 5)
        - G619, Chudnovsky, David. Conference material,1986 (Box 105, Folder 6)
        - G626[b,c,d], McCarthy, John. Papers received #1May 31, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 7)
        - G626[b,c,d], McCarthy, John. Papers received #2May 31, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 8)
        - G633, Jubien, Michael. Property Theory: A Draft, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 9)
        - G650, Partee, Barbara. Papers received #1Sept. 16, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 10)
        - G650, Partee, Barbara. Papers received #2Sept. 16, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
        - G675, Kuroda, S.-Y. Papers received #11985 (Box 106, Folder 2)
        - G675, Kuroda, S.-Y. Papers received #21985 (Box 106, Folder 3)
        - G675a, Kuroda, S.-Y. SDF Workshop in Japanese Syntax (Box 106, Folder 4)
        - G741, Denicoff, Marvin. Materials receivedNov. 19, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 5)
        - G751, Anderson, John. Papers received1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 6)
        - G773, Peters, Stanley. Report of Workshop on Information and Representation,1985 (Box 106, Folder 7)
        - G817, Brady, J. Michael. Studies of Algebraic Theorem Proving in Geometry, Nov. 1985 (Proceedings 1985 IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation, Mar. 1985) (Box 106, Folder 8)
        - G817, Brady, J. Michael. Robotics Research: the Third International Symposium, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 1)
        - G817, Brady, J. Michael. Robotics Research: the Fourth International Symposium,1988 (Box 107, Folder 2)
        - G849, Kuno, Susumu. Japanese Syntax Workshop, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 3)
        - G850, Goslin, David. Final Report of the Ten-Year Outlook on Research Opportunities in the Behavioral and Social Sciences: draftSept. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 4)
        - G850, Goslin, David. The Behavioral and Social Sciences: Achievements and Opportunities, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 5)
        - G863, Raibert, Marc. Legged Robots That Balance, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 1)
        - G892, Stryker, Michael. Papers, 1986-1987 (Box 108, Folder 2)
        - G910, Bolles, Robert. Preprints of the Fourth International Symposium of Robotics Research #11987 (Box 108, Folder 3)
        - G910, Bolles, Robert. Preprints of the Fourth International Symposium of Robotics Research #21987 (Box 108, Folder 4)
        - G912, Langendoen, D. Terrence. LSA Bulletin, no. 104, June 1984 (Box 108, Folder 5)
        - G914, Kraft, Donald. Proceedings of the Tenth Annual International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research & Development in Information Retrieval,1987 (Box 108, Folder 6)
        - G969a, Stanford University/SDF Archives. Progress report, June 1989 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B. Preprogram Grant Requests
    SDF received requests for funding between 1970-1980; although, it was not yet distributing funds. Similarly from 1981-1982, prior to formalization of their programs, funding requests were submitted to the Foundation. The requests were kept on file, and in 1983, when the full filing system was imposed, the set was numbered as the "900,000" series. Preprogram requests were in some cases initial contacts made by institutions or individual researchers whose projects were funded after the Foundation's programs began.
    - Subsubseries 1. Grant Requests, 1970 - 1980
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 1-7, 1970-1974 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 8-10, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 11-15, 1973-1974 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 16, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 17-25, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 26-33, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 6)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 34-38, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 7)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 39-41, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 42-44, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 45-50, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 10)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 51, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 52-57, 1974-1975 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 58-61, 1973-1975 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 62-63, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 64-69, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 70-81, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 82-89, 1976, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 90-95, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 96-104, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 105-108, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 109-114, 1978-1979 (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 115-122, 1978-1979 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 123-133, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 2)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 134-138, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 139-145, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 146-149, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 150-159, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 160-169, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 170-172, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 173-180, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 181-192, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 10)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 193-195, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 11)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 196-200, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 12)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 201-209, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 210, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 211-214, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 215-224, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Grant requests, Part I. No. 225-235, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Grant requests, Part II. No. 1-7,1980 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Grant requests, Part II. No. 8-11,1980 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Grant requests, Part III. No. 1-9,1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Grant requests, Part III. No. 10-22,1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Subsubseries 2. Grant Requests: 1983 Numbering Series, 1981 - 1982
      - 900165-900168, Feb.-Mar., Sept.-Nov. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - 900169-900172, Oct.-Dec. 1980, Feb.-June 1981 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - 900173, Nov. 1980-Apr. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - 900174-900179, Feb.-Mar. 1979, Nov. 1980, Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - 900180, Jan.-Mar. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - 900181, Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - 900182-900184, Jan.-Feb. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - 900185, Mar. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - 900186-900190, Mar.-Apr. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - 900191-900197, Apr.-June 1981 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - 900198-900200, Apr.-June 1981, Feb. 1982 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - 900201-900203, May-June, Aug. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - 900204-900207, June-July, Oct. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - 900208, June 1981 (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - 900209, #1May-June 1981 (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - 900209, #2May-June 1981 (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - 900210-900212, July 1981 (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - 900213-900218, June-July 1981 (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - 900219, July 1981 (Box 113, Folder 19)
      - [NOTE: No number 900220 was received at Stanford.] (Box 113, Folder 19.5)
      - 900221-900226, July-Aug. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 20)
      - 900227-900228, May-Oct. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 21)
      - 900229, Oct. 1980, Feb.-May 1981 (Box 113, Folder 22)
      - 900230, Oct. 1980, Feb. 1981 (Box 113, Folder 23)
      - 900231-900232, Mar.-May 1981 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C. Turned-down proposals
    This subseries consists of two types of proposals not funded. SDF kept the preprogram requests which were not funded separate from requests which were numbered according to the arrangement devised in 1983. There are also a few early requests which were discovered by SDF staff in August, 1984, not to have been acted upon. These were assigned numbers in the current series, and notes were placed in their files identifying them as "fadeaways."
    - Subsubseries 1. 1983 Numbering Series, 1981-1982
      - 900000-900002, Oct. 1981-Mar. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - 900003, #1Feb.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - 900003, #2Feb.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - 900003, #3Feb.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - 900004, Aug.-Oct. 1981 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - 900005, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - 900006, Apr. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - 900006, #1Feb. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - 900006, #2Feb. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - 900007-900008, Mar.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - 900009, Mar.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - 900010-900011, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - 900012, Apr.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 13)
      - 900013, Apr.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - 900014, Apr. 1982 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - 900015-900016, May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 16)
      - 900017, Mar. 1982-Feb. 1983 (Box 114, Folder 17)
      - 900018, May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - 900019, #1Apr.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 19)
      - 900019, #2Apr.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 20)
      - 900019, #3Apr.-May 1982 (Box 114, Folder 21)
      - 900020, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - 900021, Mar.-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - 900022, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - 900023-900024, Sept. 1981-Mar. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - 900025, Mar.-Aug. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - 900027, May 1982 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - 900028-900029, June-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - 900030, May-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - 900031, May, July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - 900031. Slides (Box 115, Folder 10)
      - 900032, Mar.-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - 900033-900034, Mar.-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - 900035, #1Aug. 1981 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - 900035, #2Aug. 1981 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - 900036,June 1981 (Box 115, Folder 15)
      - 900037,#1 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - 900037,#2 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      - 900038,Mar.-July 1982 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      - 900040, #1Jan. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 19)
      - 900040, #2Jan. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 20)
      - 900041-900042,Dec. 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 21)
      - 900043,Feb. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 22)
      - 900044,Feb. 1982 (Box 115, Folder 23)
      - 900045, #1Dec. 1981 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - 900045, #2Dec. 1981 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      - 900046, #1Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - 900046, #2Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - 900047-900049, Dec. 1981-Aug. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 5)
      - 900050, #1Feb. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      - 900050, #2Feb. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - 900051, Feb. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - 900052-900053, Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - 900054-900055, Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - 900056-900057, Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      - 900058, #1Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - 900058, #2Mar. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - 900059, #1Feb.-July 1982 (Box 116, Folder 14)
      - 900059, #2Feb.-July 1982 (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - 900059, #3Feb.-July 1982 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      - 900059, #4Feb.-July 1982 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - 900059, Aug. 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - 900059, July-Nov. 1981 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - 900060, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - 900061-900062, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - 900063, #1Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - 900063, #2Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - 900063, #3Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - 900064-900065, Mar. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - 900066, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - 900067, Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - 900068, #1Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - 900068, #2Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - 900068, #3Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - 900068, #4Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      - 900068, #5Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - 900068, #6Oct. 1980-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - 900069, Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 14)
      - 900070, Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 15)
      - 900071-900075, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      - 900076-900077, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 117, Folder 17)
      - 900078, Aug. 1981 (Box 117, Folder 18)
      - 900079, #1July 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - 900079, #2July 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - 900079, #3July 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - 900080-900081, Dec. 1981-Mar. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - 900082, Dec. 1981 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - 900083-900084, Jan.-Feb. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - 900085, July-Aug. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - 900086-900087, May 1981 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      - 900088, Proposal,Feb. 1981 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - 900088, Supplemental material, #1Jan. 1981 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      - 900088, Supplemental material #2Jan. 1981 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      - 900088, Supplemental material, Aug. 1980 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      - 900089-900091, Aug.-Sept. 1981, Apr.-May 1982 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      - 900092-900097, Apr.-May 1982 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      - 900098-900102, May-June 1982 (Box 118, Folder 15)
      - 900103-900106, June 1982 (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - 900107, Oct. 1981, June 1982 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      - 900108-900110, June 1982, Aug. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      - 900111-900115, May-July 1982 (Box 118, Folder 19)
      - 900116-900121, June-Aug. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 20)
      - 900122, July-Aug. 1982 (Box 118, Folder 21)
      - 900123, July-Aug. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - 900124-900125, Nov.-Dec. 1981, July-Aug. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - 900126, Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - 900127-900129, Jan.-Feb. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - 900130, Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - 900131-900132, Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - 900133-900135, Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - 900136, Feb.-Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - 900137-900141, Feb.-Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - 900142-900146, Apr., June 1982 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - 900147-900151, Mar. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - 900152-900154, Feb.-Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - 900155, Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - 900156, Proposal and correspondence, Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - 900156, Proposal Appendices A and B, Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      - 900156, Proposal Appendix C, #1Apr. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      - 900156, Proposal Appendix C, #2Apr. 1982 [NOTE: There is an overlap of 900165 and 900166 because they were numbered retroactively c. Jan. 1983, and 900157 and 900158 were skipped.] (Box 119, Folder 17)
      - 900159-900161, Aug.-Oct. 1981 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      - 900162-900164, Dec. 1981-Jan. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 19)
      - 900165-900166, Aug. 1982 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Subsubseries 2. Turned-down files, 1981 - 1988
      - T10, Proposal, Sept. 1981 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - T13d, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1986-Apr. 1987 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - T14, Background information, 1981, Aug. 1984 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      - T17c, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      - T17c, Proposal, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      - T21, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Oct. 1983 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      - T21, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-Oct. 1982 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      - T35, Background information and correspondence, Mar.-Aug. 1982 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - T42, Proposal, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      - T42, Background information (Box 120, Folder 10)
      - T43, Proposal, notes and correspondence, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      - T43, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-Nov. 1982 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      - T43, Reprint package, Aug.-Sept. 1982 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      - T49b, Budget, photographs and notes,c. May 1984 (Box 120, Folder 14)
      - T49b, Proposal, Apr. 1984 (Box 120, Folder 15)
      - T49b, Section D with photographs (Box 120, Folder 16)
      - T49b, Photographs (Box 120, Folder 17)
      - T49b, Notes and correspondence, Apr.-May 1984 (Box 120, Folder 18)
      - T49b, Notes. SDF Director of Program Administration, Oct. 1983-Feb. 1984 (Box 120, Folder 19)
      - T49b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Feb. 1984 (Box 120, Folder 20)
      - T54, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1984 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - T54, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-Dec.1983 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - T54, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June-Nov. 1982 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - T54, Reprints. Emilio Bizzi. (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - T54, Reprints. Neville Hogan: Control of robots (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - T54, Reprints. Neville Hogan: Control of movement in biological systems (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - T54, Reprints. Neville Hogan: Processing of myoeletric activity (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - T54. Reprints. John M. Hollerbach (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - T55b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Nov. 1983-July 1984 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - T58c, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Apr.-May, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      - T60, Correspondence and clipping, Oct. 1982-July 1984 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - T60, Proposal as presented to SDF Board of Trustees, Apr. 1982 (Box 121, Folder 12)
      - T60, Background information (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - T67, Correspondence and budget proposal, Mar.-Apr. 1983 (Box 121, Folder 14)
      - T67, Book draft: Information and computation, Mar. 1983 (Box 121, Folder 15)
      - T67, Background information #1 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - T67, Background information #2 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - T71, Machine Perception. Ramakant Nevatia (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - T87b, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1984 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - T89, Proposal and correspondence, July 1982-Dec. 1983 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - T89, Proposal and background papers, Apr.-Aug. 1982 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - T90, Proposal, notes and correspondence,Jan.-Nov. 1983 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - T90, Proposal and correspondence, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - T101, The Information Professional: Survey of an Emerging Field. Anthony Debons, Donald W. King, Una Mansfield, Donald L. Shiney. (Box 122, Folder 9)
      - T113c, Proposal and correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1984 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      - T113c, Proposal attachments #1 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      - T113c, Proposal attachments #2 (Box 122, Folder 12)
      - T113c, Proposal attachments #3 (Box 122, Folder 13)
      - T120, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Mar.-June 1982 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - T120, Background information #1 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - T120, Background information #2 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - T125, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1982-Aug. 1983 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - T129, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1982 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - T134, Notes and correspondence, June-Aug. 1983 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - T134, Proposal, May 1983 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      - T134, Proposal, Curriculum vitae (Box 123, Folder 8)
      - T134, Proposal attachments, #1May 1983 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      - T134, Proposal attachments, #2May 1983 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      - T134, Preliminary proposal,July 1982 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      - T136c, Proposal, notes and correspondence, June 1986-May 1987 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      - T136c, Site visit materials, March 1987 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - T142, Proposal, notes and correspondence, 1983-July 1984 (Box 123, Folder 14)
      - T142, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Jan.-Aug. 1982 (Box 123, Folder 15)
      - T142, Background information #1 (Box 123, Folder 16)
      - T142, Background information #2 (Box 123, Folder 17)
      - T142, Background information #3 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      - T162, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1982-Sept. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - T162, Background information (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - T164, Background information, 1981 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - T172b, Preliminary correspondence, July 1983 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - T184, Background information (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - T189, Proposal, notes and correspondence, Aug. 1982-Dec. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - T213, Proposal, notes and correspondence, May.-Aug. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - T213, Proposal,Mar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - T213, Proposal, Appendix AMar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - T213, Proposal, Appendix BMar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - T213, Proposal, Appendix CMar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 11)
      - T213, Proposal, Appendices D-LMar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 12)
      - T213, Proposal, notes and correspondence,Sept. 1982-Mar. 1983 (Box 124, Folder 13)